Yuzuki
Poor Yuzuki. She was crying.
They're only one building away from a Tetris.
And then the whole city might just disappear on us.
If that does happen, I wonder if whatever's making Yuzuki sad will disappear too.
Hey, Grandma, I'm finally…
About time.
We've been wondering when you were going to get home.
Yuzuki was nice enough to help with dinner tonight, such an angel.
Not to mention a real whiz in the kitchen.
Oh, stop it. You're embarrassing me.
What the what?
It's valid.
Physics
We're in offerings come into finally a person.
The truth is, in the infinity holes in the mind.
We come into the show.
Federation-san, please, your father and hypocrite.
Thank you.
So, Yuzuki...
Thanks to a belly full of food and a hot bath, now I'm all inner charge!
Aurichalcum attack!
No!
Hey, cut it out!
Take that!
Please! That tickles, Yuzuki! Stop it!
Quit it!
Knock it off!
Bad girl!
Yeah, so I'm... I'm sorry.
I was really mean to you.
Why not?
Because I have no idea what you're thinking, Ruko!
I don't know what she's thinking. It scares me.
It's okay! No biggie. It's nothing to apologize for.
The truth is, I was so afraid of losing to Akira the whole time.
I was upset, and then it just ended in the worst way.
Oh.
That's not all.
There's this boy I like.
But...
We can never be together.
What?
Come on now, don't think like that.
Hey, I'm sure this guy will fall for you.
It won't happen.
And it shouldn't either.
I just wish...
These feelings would go away.
Hold on a sec.
This guy you have a thing for, it's not...
It's not...
Time!
Stop it, you tickle monster!
I wonder what it feels like to be in love.
I guess you get really excited, huh?
Yeah, excited!
You know what makes Tala excited?
Battle!
What?
I love you, this girl!
This girl...
What?
I like the cool...
Kazuki?
Oh, she went home already?
Yeah, a while ago.
Okay. Thanks so much.
Hitue comes here to study and practice battle strategies.
She takes notes and that seems to help her.
So I figured it wouldn't hurt me to give it a shot.
That's a fantastic idea.
Bet you'll be kicking butt and taking names in no time.
Hitue!
And she's gone.
So, I thought about it a whole lot.
And my answer to you is yes.
So let's be friends.
Just like you asked.
Is that okay?
Of course it is!
We're friends. It's official.
Yuzuki, too!
Well, if you're okay with it.
Talking to me?
Yeah, sure. Why not?
Two friends at the same time?
We cross is just so surprising.
Huh?
You see, during that battle I had with Akira, things got so painful I started to wonder if I'd ever even want to play again.
Yeah, I know the feeling.
I knew battling as a selector would probably hurt.
But no pain, no gain, right?
We are trying to fight for a wish, after all.
Thing is, I enjoyed my battle with Ruko so much that it completely changed my tune.
It was fun.
Awesome!
I had fun, too.
Well, in that case, why don't we all play a round just for kicks?
Yeah, that's a great idea.
But we're all selectors.
So if we battle against each other, that means somebody's wish could...
Nah, don't worry about it.
As long as none of our L-rigs are in the deck, we can play the game just like normal people do.
Oh.
All right, you guys wait here, okay?
Take care, Hitu-e, and have fun.
Thanks.
All right, then.
Your turn, Hitu-e.
Let's go.
Right.
Man, when do I get to play?
Did rock, paper, scissors.
You're up next.
Finally.
Okay, summon Baromet.
What?
Wait.
Yeah, let me see.
Baromet's power level is only 7,000.
So if Yusuke has her card grow on next turn, she'd crush it in one shot, right?
Yeah, she would.
Wait, I...
Jeez, how would you like it if I gave away your strategies when you're playing?
Oh, sorry.
Tomo wants battle!
You and Ruko are really alike, aren't you?
Well, I guess Hitu-e's wish already came true.
So she doesn't need to battle anymore.
It seems not.
You okay with that?
I am.
But that means you're...
It's fine.
No, wait!
Not that one!
Right.
So sorry.
Well, you are helping me.
So there's no need to apologize.
We're friends now, right, you big doofus?
So...
Friends tease and call each other names, huh?
All the time!
Try calling us something dumb.
Like Stinky or Jerk.
Just do it.
It's not like we'll get mad.
Um, okay.
Well, here goes.
Hi, Stinky.
Hi, Jerk.
I've never seen Hitu-e smile like that.
I have to admit, I sometimes wish I wasn't her L-Rig.
Well, there's no point in torturing yourself.
I suppose not.
Tama likes Roo!
Likes Roo a whole lot!
Likes being your L-Rig!
Yay, Roo!
Yes, but...
It's okay.
After all, Tama and Roo are friends.
Wait a sec.
You mean...
Right.
Tama doesn't know.
I see.
Yes!
I'm next!
Jeez, you really like me across, don't you?
Yeah, I sure do.
A lot!
Yeah, I saw her out in the front!
Oh, really?
Yes, Akira's here!
You mean the famous bottle?
Uh-huh!
Oh, I would love to see you at my hand.
Oh, no!
You're telling me Roo-Roo already went home for the day?
That's so mean.
She broke her promise to meet me.
What a lousy thing to do.
Yeah, tell me about it.
How dare she stand you up?
Do you want us to go make her sorry?
Mm-mm.
I'm sure she had a real good reason.
Oh, well.
Just have to try tomorrow.
Oh, wait!
What happens if she leaves before I get here again?
I wish someone could keep tabs on her.
But that's just crazy talk, because who would want to do that?
Ooh, I'd be happy to.
Yeah, me too.
Leave it to us, okay?
I'm so wonderful.
I wonder where Tama's the life is.
I think it's really tasty.
Aw, thank you girls so much.
I've got a shoot to get to, so Tama's.
Yeah!
I don't want to go home.
You can't keep hiding from Kazuki like this forever.
Yeah, I know, but...
Yuzuki!
It's Akira.
She was at school this afternoon.
Dang, Ruko, you won again.
Booyah!
That means you get me a milk tea.
I'll take some sweet bean soup while you're up.
Sure, Grandma.
Oh, man.
I lose a game, and all of a sudden, I'm you guys' personal waiter.
Chop, chop, garçon!
Yes, ma'am.
Glad to see you're in better spirits.
Huh?
Well, are you ready for a game against me, Rue?
The loser will have to clean the bathroom.
What?
No way!
You're too good!
I like playing for fun against Grandma and Ayumu like this.
But, to be honest, I like battling along with Tama even more.
Not just for fun, but on a battlefield.
In matches against other selectors.
It's weird, though.
In those battles, everyone's fighting so hard for their wishes.
And even though I don't have one, I want to keep fighting harder, too.
What's that, dear?
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's my turn, right?
Aki was looking for me?
Yeah.
She must want to battle against you pretty bad, Rukov.
That stalker just doesn't give up.
Yeah, but I don't even have a wish like the other selectors do.
So, I guess there wouldn't be any harm in fighting her then, would there?
No, you're wrong!
Whatever you do, please don't battle Akira, okay?
Um, sure.
Listen.
She's gonna do anything to get you to fight, but you just have to ignore her.
She might even try to turn your friends against you.
Oh, I'm not worried about that.
It's just you and Hitoi, and I trust you guys.
Ruru!
So glad you're finally here.
Yeah, I'll say.
So what up, girlfriend?
Huh?
Oh, guess what?
We all just got a really cool text from Akira.
She's got a shoot this afternoon, and she said we can come if we bring you.
She'll give us a tour of the studio if we all go together.
There's a chance we might get to meet Iona, too.
Sorry.
Appreciate the offer, but we've already got plans.
You weren't invited, so shut your face!
What?
Come on, Ruru.
Come with us.
Um, but I...
Watch yourself.
There is no stronger bond of friendship than a mutual enemy, Frankfurt Moore.
All right.
That's about it for today, class.
Tomorrow we'll start with...
Ruku, time to go.
Yusuki?
Talk about rude.
Where do you get off barging your way in here and ordering our friend around like that?
She's not your friend.
Ruku?
Coming!
You're going with us!
Hey, what's all this about?
You stay out of it, stubbleface.
What?
Stubbleface?
After them!
And send out a text to everybody!
I've spotted them!
Go!
Move it, you jerk!
Over here!
Right!
Oh, I really want to hang out with Akira.
No!
Yusuki, look.
It's okay.
It's no big deal if I gotta battle her.
But it is.
Let me put it this way.
Remember when I said I wish I knew what you were thinking?
Yeah.
Still do.
But there is one thing I know for certain about you.
You really like Wee Cross battles.
You're so happy when you play.
But battling Akira is awful.
It's painful.
Trust me, I know from experience.
And I'm worried that playing her will make you hate the game.
I don't want that to happen.
Yusuki.
Down this way?
That's what the first year said.
This isn't good.
I'll draw them outside and distract them.
So you just stay put, okay?
No.
Wait.
Hey, don't worry.
Be back soon.
What?
Here they are!
Don't let them get away!
Dang it all.
I'm grateful to have a friend who's so worried about me.
But the truth is...
It's better if she doesn't know.
And I can't even explain it.
But I still want to do this for some reason.
Am I nuts?
Why do I want to battle Akira so bad?
It's all I can think about.
Ruu!
Ruu and Tama are the same!
Want to battle Akira too!
There's something scary about her.
But she and I...
We're the same.
She's frightening.
I don't know what Ruko's thinking.
There's something...
Scary about her.
That's not true!
No!
Hey!
Ruu-Ruu.
Come out and play.
Guess who's here?
Whoa!
Awesome sauce!
Ladies!
Thank you so much!
You asked and we delivered!
You are the best up top!
Well, Ruu-Ruu?
Let's go!
Um, Akira?
What about us?
Yeah, I've got to shoot.
Get lost.
But I thought you said we could hang out with you.
A top model like me hanging with a bunch of uggos?
Not likely.
Mm-mm.
No one's gonna bother us in here, Ruu-Ruu.
So you're ready to throw down?
Or what?
No one's gonna bother us in here, Ruu-Ruu.
This is it.
I'm gonna play against Akira.
Hey.
If you're looking for a battle, give me a shot.
That's...
Damn it!
You skank-ass hoes!
Stop trying to steal my opponents!
You misunderstand.
I'm challenging you.
What?
It seems you only like to prey on rookies.
Guess you're just scared of me.
Akira!
Huh?
I've been looking all over for you.
Come on, you're up.
No, wait, I, um, I need a few minutes, okay?
We don't have a few minutes.
No!
Stop shoving!
It won't take long, I swear!
We've got a whole crew waiting on you, so get the lead out.
Um, thanks for that great fake-out.
What fake-out?
I was serious.
Huh?
You wanted to have a battle, didn't you?
Uh...
Perhaps you had a grudge with Akira.
No, wait.
That's not it.
You'll battle anybody.
Anything to get your fix.
Am I right?
I am right.
So battle me.
Wait a minute.
You have no wish.
Participating as a selector without having a wish is more than just wrong.
It's blasphemy.
That won't go unpunished.
Wait.
Blasphemy?
You have no wish.
今日の祈りは明日多分になる
天と地を映す逆さまの名誉
回りだした歯車
人混みの中で耳を澄ましたら
魂を召くあの鈴の音
Thank you.
A WeCross party?
I might even find another selector to battle.
All this time, I never noticed.
I just can't get my hair tied up right, that's all.
I don't want to hear you talk like that ever again.
She was also kind of scary.
Next time, that invalidated vow.